

# **VICTOR HUERTA**

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a current Computer Science student with a wide knowledge on technology. I am an enthusiast on computers and technology. I'm very open to learn any new skill I'm required or would be helpful for me and my job. I moved to USA almost five years ago from Mexico. (Green card holder). Since I moved here I've been working for a construction company as my first job here. since I recently was sent to unemployment ( Due to no enough work), and now I'm able to speak English, I'm trying to move forwards to finding a job on the IT field. I'm very hard worker. You can ask my actual employer.

### **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

## College Of The Canyons

Computer Science | 2017- currently

- Studied programing fundamental for Java, C++, C, Java Script, also some html and scss3.
- I also did take and pass Comp A+ computer maintenance class (I do not have the certification YET, but this is my actual goal, I'm preparing to take the 220-1001 & 220-1002 CompTIA A+ exams in order to obtain my certification).
- I did learn almost all my English here. (I'm native Spanish speaker)

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Construction Worker

Icon West Coast Construction. | March 2016 - present

- Replacing and installing tiles.
- Construction tools experience.(Drill, Zaw-saw, skill-saw...)
- Driving, loading, unloading materials on truck.
- Basic carpenter skills
- Able to lift over 60 ponds.
- Setting Up Concrete
- Many other construction knowledge and skills.
- 949 204-8725 (My immediate supervisor)

## Universidad Tecnologica de Nayarit

IT Engeniering 2015-2016

- I did only studied for one year before I moved to United States.
- Basic Programing
- Basic Office software
- Computer Maintenance

## Computer support service

Hospital PC | 2014 - Feb 2016 (Mexico)

- Software installations.
- Computer maintenance(parts upgrading, cleaning, files recovering, back ups)
- Driving to transport consumables and pc parts.
- Filling documentation.
- costumer support.
- Cashier and some inventory experience
- PC building